gamesgirls.club 2018-09-10

# Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of all Internet users.

**Information collected:**   
When you visit GamesGirls.club we collect some information from you. We collect no personally identifiable information such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you willingly submit it to us via registration or contact. Some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use is collected upon your visit to our site in order to provide our advertisers with targeting information. 

**Cookies and data collected:**   
GamesGirls.club collects information about the way visitors and players are using our website through the use of Google Analytics and its related cookie(s). The goal of collecting this data is to make better informed decisions about what games our users are more likely to enjoy and to help improve the experience on GamesGirls.club. The type of information that Google Analytics collects includes browser and operating system type, country, pages visited, time spent on site, date/time stamp and broad demographic information. Google Analytics does not collect any personally identifiable information about you on GamesGirls.club.

Certain games on GamesGirls.club will create "Local shared objects" which allow the game to save game progress so that when you return you can pick up from where you left off. Any game save data is stored only on your computer and not transferred to GamesGirls.club or any other third party. Some games from third-party publishers that are included on GamesGirls.club may offer the ability to save game-progress in the cloud via third-party servers, in which the storage and retrieval of such data is dictated by the privacy policy of such game publisher offering the service. 

**External Links:**   
GamesGirls.club may link to other web sites and is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these external sites. Some games on GamesGirls.club also contain links to external sites or may contain requests for personal information for gameplay purposes (e.g. account registration or chatroom features) which are governed by their own individual privacy policies. All users should therefore also be aware of the individual privacy policies within any game that requests personal information such as name or email address. 

**Advertising:** GamesGirls.club is a free to use website and generates revenue through third-party advertising on the website. Without the support of this advertising GamesGirls.club would not be able to provide new games. These third-party advertising companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites to help determine which advertisements are most suited to your interests and measure performance of any advertising campaigns. In order to collect this information, the third-party may use a cookie or other such as javascript codes. GamesGirls.club has no influence over the policies of third-party advertising networks (except our ability to discontinue using their services).   
If you would like more information about advertising practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit [ Google's Advertising and Privacy page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

**Opt Out of targeted advertising:**   
Targeted advertising using browser behavior is designed to ensure users see more relevant advertising based on their interests. If you prefer not to see targeted advertising from our advertising partners you can opt out of these services by following the below links:   
Google: Please [click here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922) for Google’s opt out process 

**Children under 13:**   
We are committed to complying with the children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). GamesGirls.club has no user forums, registration systems, chat or instant message capabilities, and thus no private information pertaining to children can be shared on GamesGirls.club. However certain games hosted on GamesGirls.club may have such features as described in the External Links section, and are governed by their own individual privacy policy. If you have any concern that information related to the privacy of children has been submitted to GamesGirls.club, please [contact us](mailto:alexshtoss@gmail.com)

**Updates to this Privacy Policy:**   
This Privacy Policy may be changed or modified from time to time. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to this page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back to our Privacy Policy periodically. 

**General & Contact us:**   
By using this site, you accept the GamesGirls.club Online Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns please [contact us](mailto:alexshtoss@gmail.com). We hope you continue to enjoy your experience on GamesGirls.club.
